I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Arm up! Higher, higher...Don't let go.
Good...Don't forget
how that felt. Hold it!
What's the Marquee?
It's the place where
every band in the country
dreams of playing just once...
It's like the Holy Land for bands.
It's great that you're going to play there!
We're just playing for
the daytime auditions, though.
Still, it's great! It's the Marquee!
Yes. That's what I think, too!
In time, we'll be able to
do a live concert at night.
Yeah...
Uh...Would it be okay
if I came to see you?
Yeah. Come. Absolutely!!
Saku...
That band's...no good.
But boss!
No, no...One look at them
was all I needed.
TV Head...I'm pretty
confident of that band...
"Self Revival: A Reclusive Life Magazine"
TV Head...I'm pretty
confident of that band...
"Self Revival: A Reclusive Life Magazine"
Hmm...I haven't seen
any promising bands lately.
"Self Revival: A Reclusive Life Magazine"
You think so?
Maybe it's about time for me
to get out of this business...
Are you serious?
And...what about the bands here today?
Well...
There's P.W.M. From Yokohama,
and a band called Beck...
Beck? Stupid name...
What's the matter, Koyuki? Nervous?
Well, this place is...
What's the matter? Where're your balls?
You too, Chiba-kun...
Come on. Do your best, everybody!
It looks like it. It looks just like it.
Huh? What does?
Saku!
The guitar that the guy
with the long hair has.
Hmm...I know I've seen it before...
"Live 18
'Leon Sykes'"
Huh? He lost a string.
"Live 18
'Leon Sykes'"
Uh!
-Hey, Koyuki!
-Typhoon!
Typhoon 24! 24-7 non...
Oh...Why? At the very start...
Why'd my string break?
Hmm...
Yukio! You're too loud!
Okay!
"Fishing Hole"
Yeah...No...Uh...Got it.
Yeah. Just send me a sample, anyway.
Bye...
Ryusuke-kun...
Huh? What is it?
Uh...I wanted you to listen to this.
Oh? You made this?
Yeah...
I see.
Oh...Sorry about that. It's just
so much like a Dying Breed song.
It was funny. I'm sorry.
Mm...Now that you mention it,
it is similar.
Don't worry. My first song
was pretty bad, too.
There's another song.
Huh?
The song you just heard was
written about a month ago.
There's another one...
that I wrote last night...
Your talent amazes me.
Really?
Yeah, well...It's not such a great song,
but there's something that stands out.
This part...let's see...
What if you did this?
The chords that you're using...
I can't figure out what they are...
Heh...I see. I'm not sure myself.
I guess you can say they're my chords.
Your chords?
No one ever taught me.
I didn't study with books, either.
You learned by ear?
That's why I don't know my scales at all.
Oh...
I guess it's feeling...
Yes...feeling.
Wow! Looks like Taira-san's band
is playing at the Marquee next.
Hmm...
I hear they get at least
200 demo tapes every month.
Hmm...Is that so?
Oh! Beck's playing at
the Whisky a GoGo, too!
Wow!
Hmm...
Huh?
Uh! Yeah!
You open up the door
with negative aura
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
If you never change
I think there is no way
my life fizzle out
You open up the door
with negative aura
(I'm fed up fed up fed up)
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
(I can't keep up with you)
I think there is no way
my life fizzle out
If you are at a loss as to what to do.
Raise your stiff middle finger.
It will know which way the wind blows.
Oh! The kid broke another string.
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't benumb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
That kid's good...
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't benumb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let...
I think it's good. 100 times better
than the other one.
But the good parts are
almost all Ryusuke's ideas.
I see...
Koyuki!
Huh?
When you write new songs, let me
hear them first again, will you?
Sure! I'll dump this song
and pump out more new ones!
Oh...It's so hard to get the F.
Don't worry. There's no reason to hurry.
Just learn to play each chord clearly.
Koyuki-kun...Is something wrong?
Uh...I'm sorry.
To think that I'm teaching
someone to play the guitar...
Why? Koyuki, you're really
good at the guitar!
Isn't that right, Saku-chan?
Are you all right?
Ouch...
I...I can feel the passion...
-Huh?
I...When I see Koyuki-kun
and Saku-chan playing...
My passion burns and I feel
like I have to do my best, too!
Straighten your spine!
Pull your body up!
Keep your balance! Don't waver!
Hiromi-chan's really
trying hard, isn't she?
-Yeah...
-Slowly...Keep it level...
This is where you can show
your skill. Yes! Very good!
She's a really nice girl.
Oh...Did I keep you waiting?
No. Not at all.
Where's Maho?
She isn't coming today.
Hmm...
I...I might become the
older brother of a celebrity.
Huh?!
Even as we speak...She's probably
eating something really good
with the boss of Yoshito's talent agency.
-Huh?
-Agency?
W-W-What?!
Are you serious?!
That's supposed to be a
pretty big agency, right?
A celebrity? She's come a long way.
She's zipped right by us!
Maho...
Hmm...
Say, how's the band coming along?
Well, we're working real hard.
Think you'll sell?
-If we can continue the way we are...
-That's no good!
Why?
You look like an average kid...
Instead of fiddling around,
you should get yourself an honest job.
I...
Kid...Don't take this world lightly!
Listen...The people around you
won't do anything to help you.
They'll just amuse themselves
with you for a while.
Hey! Saku! Hurry up, will you?!
Uh...That guy with the skinny eyes...
Please let go of the rope.
Hey, Saku! You sure you've got balls?!
I can't go on...
But, that Koyuki is hanging in there...
It sounds like his voice has
gotten louder lately, but...
Maybe swimming has
increased his lung capacity.
That means that Saito-san
isn't just a nuisance...
Hey! Quit hanging around!
Oh, Tanaka-kun! It's been a while.
Momoko-sensei!
I'm ready for my lesson, Kenichi-san!
Kenichi...san?
Ohh...Momoko-sensei...
You look wonderful in swimwear, too.
Squeeze your sweat yeah
Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat
Find the way you are,
spice of your life
Heavy beat, hey come on people
Find the way you are,
spice of your life
Heavy beat, hey come on people
Yeah take your spice
Yeah find my wife
That long-haired guitarist
seems a bit menacing...
Yeah find my wife
Yeah take your spice
Aha...I remember now...that guitar...
-What do you mean?
-It's Lucille.
Find my wife
They've really got it
over the other bands.
We might see an increase in membership.
Yeah, well...They're still not good
enough for us to put them on at night.
Huh? At night?
Running over sometimes
Feel like you leave me behind
Now you don't have to mind it
Find you shining...Everyday by day
Sing it up, my sister
In this world which
everyone is lonely
Everything will be fine someday
Remember playing in the backyard
Hiding myself in garage
It might be interesting
to pit them against Hitode.
Hiding myself in garage
It might be interesting
to pit them against Hitode.
Since you never could catch me
What?! But Hitode is our monthly regular
and our number one draw.
Since you never could catch me
Find you crying
weeping in darkness
Sing it up...
She didn't come today, either...
Right, Koyuki-chan!
Oh, you talking about Maho?
She's meeting with the agency again today.
Has the date of her debut
been determined?
No. Maho doesn't seem to be very eager.
They've been trying to convince her.
Oh? Then I'll take her place.
Are you crazy?
You see...If I took my clothes off,
it would really be shocking...
It really would be shocking...
-Koyuki-kun...Orange juice?
-What are you looking at? Oh, please!
Uh...Thanks.
How did I do?
Here. I'll give this to you.
Oh...Beck's CD!
But...Why are you called Beck?
Well...It's a dog.
A dog?
That's right. It's the name
of Ryusuke-kun's dog.
What a funny name for a dog...
Yeah...and his looks, too.
Really? I'd like to meet him.
I don't know about that...
Besides, I don't think the band name
is Beck in America, anyway.
In America?
Holy shit!
That bastard...
I shouldn't have left it to Albin...
Fuck!
Flight 765 from London is delayed
due to weather conditions.
Well then...What's the
purpose of your trip here?
For business.
You know, I'm organizing
a big festival here.
And uh...
What else?
I'm looking for a treasure.
A what?!
-Promotion of the
Grateful Sound Summer Special
-(The promotion...)
Is the key to the success of this festival.
So we have invited Japanese producer,
Mr. Ran, former member of Noir,
and American Leon Sykes,
President of RJ Label.
I got a preview of
your movie the other day...
Dying Breed's concert tour movie...
Oh, Jim Walsh's latest release?
That's right. And there's a
Japanese boy who appears in that movie.
Oh? What does that boy do?
He sings on stage with Dying Breed.
A Japanese?
Sounds interesting.
Uh...Mr. Leon Sykes
should be here shortly.
Pardon me...
Mr. Sykes has disappeared from his hotel.
What did you say?
What's that?!
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
A movie about music?
Sid and Nancy was good.
"Live 19 'Blues'"
A movie about music?
Sid and Nancy was good.
"Live 19 'Blues'"
Gary Oldman was skinny.